[Music]
hello everyone this is Rahul zakara from
sherka welcome back to exciting 3
actionable stock updates 3 basically
means right sector right quality and
right valuation these are our investment
ideas today we have an update on Sant
R our analyst has a positive view on
sunch realy moving to its strong growth
Outlook over the medium to long term the
company reported threee sales growth of
26% year- on-ear for quarter 4 of FY 24
at R 678 cres and 20% year on- year for
full year FY 24 at rupees 1,915 cres it
remains on track to achieve it pre-sales
growth guidance of 20 to 25% year on-ear
for FY 25 Business Development will
remain in focus with the recent
acquisition of the Bandstand project the
expected acquisition of the napan road
the addition of the Bor only project and
the IFC platform deals it remains on
track to increase its average rental
income perom to rupees 320 CR in F28
from R 35 CR in FY 24 at an overall
capex of R
950 next we cover ICI
Lombard our analyst maintains buy rating
on IC Lombard with a price target of
rupees
1,950 ICC Lombard reported strong
performance in quarter 4 led by healthy
premium growth Improvement in Combined
ratio and higher investment income
management is confident about further
Improvement in Combined ratio in fi25 we
expect premium growth to be in the
higher meetings led by investment in the
distribution Channel and leveraging
digital capabilities gradual Improvement
in the combined ratios should boost
profitability we remain optimistic about
the company's plan to grow in calibrated
manner we expect the company to deliver
Ro of 18 to 20% over the medium TP at
the current market price the stock
trades at 34.4 d SEI 25 and 28.8 times
at SEI 26 estimated EPS the stock has
outperformed the broader indexes in last
months investment in Securities Market
are subject to Market risks read all the
related documents carefully before
investing